Board meeting for Monday, August 21st, 2023, my invocation in the past year. One church was for her, you know.
I was bright. I'd bother our guide, we're grateful for this day. We thank you for the joy of living in the city,
Father of the State, in this great country, we ask for your, watch care guide, your son, Greg, we trust you, Lord,
and we trust in your benevolence. Thank you for your provision and all that's in Christ and we pray.
I pledge allegiance to the flag of the United States of America, and to the Republic for which it stands,
one nation under God, indivisible with liberty and justice for all.
I'm sure both of you can put on schedule personal appearances.
Statement of work with civic plus LLC, municipal code corporation for websites support and hosting in the amount of 11,449 dollars and two cents.
This is just our yearly renewal for support for city mile website. The only change is the price of 1,3 percent of the year.
We live within here, so we sit.
How long do we go on these type of services before we have them re-bid just for?
I'm sure yes.
We can look into it for next year.
We'll say that with this cost, we they fill us across that way when we do realize that.
And that's a yearly contract.
Make a motion we approve.
Second.
Assembly.
Aye.
Seven minutes from the August 7th, 2023 regular meeting.
Titchtick Client for the OSHA River 2D modeling in the amount of 12,000.
$287.52.
So, Mayor, members of the Council, there's a BA in your packet explaining this
professional service, this is the Tetra Tech, put in the OSHA River 2D modeling,
the amount of $12,087.
This comes out of our budget amount for GA claims in the amount of $750,000, which
is previously budgeted, current balance for this, because this is a previous fiscal year,
leaves a remaining balance in that budget of $244,000 and $214,000.
So again, even though we're still cleaning up some just now getting invoices for some work
being done.
The previous fiscal year, the budget for that particular item is still in means of what was
anticipated.
Most of the group.
Second.
All right.
Ma'am, good L. Stratton, Edmunds, and Palmer Client for GRDA, we live in seeing an amount
of $1,560.
So, this particular invoice is actually now into this fiscal year, which was June 22, 2018.
Again, the majority of these services were rendered in response to emails and subteen meetings
that we had for some fur filings.
Again, the 750,000 previously budget for this fiscal year, this is the first invoice
we've applied to that new budget.
So it has a remaining or will have a remaining depending on this particular invoice, the remaining
budget of 748,440 dollars.
Should I open?
Aye.
All right.
of structures and removal of various debris within the city limits of Maam Oklahoma.
Christy.
So this is a joint resolution as the mayor said to believe the cost of permits and these
associated with the new motion of various structures with an opportunity.
Most of these structures are dilapidated homes that are in the floodplain.
Some of them are dilapidated structures that have been built for more time than
the car owner.
As properties go back to the county after the tax so some of them are not livable.
And the county can be moved forward within a way some of those property rights and not charge
them a car.
We're at the still pay tipping beats.
Yeah, it's not that we don't have any to do with what they do with the degree or who's
demoing it or anything.
It's just covering the scene's constant to pull a permit for the demo.
And then we permit applications for demos, requires an inspection prior to bringing
the background to the properties, so we charge them for any of those inspection.
So is this just saying for this fiscal year?
No, this would be where I told somebody this idea wouldn't do that anymore.
What this does for us, for the city standpoint, is this money?
This is money.
We're not having this been to deal with these structures.
So do we have a list that they're going to do?
No, it's just as they come.
So I know that you've gotten a message about two 18, I,
you're less, I think, or Southwest.
That's one of the structures that they're back to the county that they're demoing.
Another one is 2G, who Southwests for the Northwest.
That's another one that caught a fire that didn't make it for a long time,
except they're demoing that.
They went back to the county.
There's one in the 400 walk of sea Southwest that they're demoing.
That's the fact that the county will be a common fire of living.
So it's just various houses on different properties that the county contains ownership.
So they do have a list right now?
I don't know if they have a list right now.
No, I have a list because they call me about purpose.
So the reason I'm asking is because can't we get a list from them of what they're planning on doing?
I can ask them for that.
Because they've got to fill in lots of people here who are waving this.
They're going to go, okay, which houses?
Because I have one next door to me, or I have one down the street to me.
They have to be owned by the county, which means they get back to the county after a tax sell.
The taxes have been paid and the money came to bill.
And most of these houses are, do you have a bill?
Because they're really close by.
Would you get a list here?
Yes.
Unless I will try to do a list.
Okay.
Because I'd like to have a list and I'd like for a month to put something else in.
We wave these and hear why.
And have a list.
At least a parcel list.
I know we can't list everything from the 50.
If you're just wanting to know about the city way.
That the county is still moving.
Yes.
Okay.
That's okay.
So I'll make a motion.
We approve.
Okay.
Bye.
Williams.
Thank you.
Bye.
11.
Q23-44 certificate of deposit agreement for $1,600, $7,800, $850 and $82 for six months
certificate of deposit to security bank and trust, you have related signing and payment
authority to the trust manager or his does he need.
Now, we've gone out best to reach the code on CDs, we've sent it out to the 7 security
bank and trust, came down at 5.5.
I don't know if it's safe, it was right.
This will pay us in six months' time, that will be around $40,000 for $1,000.
Question done.
Motion to approve.
Thank you.
Thank you, Brian.
12.
Other new businesses of many, which is a residence of the Postal Service agenda.
13 staff reports?
Yes.
I don't see my design in the course on the agenda.
It's on the Service Council.
We're sorry to say that.
We're sorry.
Which is now we would never waste your time.
14.
Just a few minutes.
15.
Motion.
Second.
Yes.
Five.